<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on iampredrag.cloud</title>
    <link>http://iampredrag.cloud/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on iampredrag.cloud</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 12:12:01 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iampredrag.cloud/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Security</title>
      <link>http://iampredrag.cloud/posts/rethinking-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 12:12:01 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iampredrag.cloud/posts/rethinking-security/</guid>
      <description>There are many reasons why I have started to write this article, and its an accumulation of several years of frustrations and experience when dealing with security in large organizations. First and foremost, there are two views on cybersecurity in the organization, one that the senior management has, and the one that the cybersecurity professionals do. So let&amp;rsquo;s try to light up some sparks&amp;hellip;
The senior management view The first thing that comes to senior management point of view is that if it isn&amp;rsquo;t the company&amp;rsquo;s core competency cybersecurity doesn&amp;rsquo;t come first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Route-based VPN between Check Point on-premise and Azure CloudGuard IaaS HA</title>
      <link>http://iampredrag.cloud/posts/checkpoint-azure-routed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 16:57:08 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iampredrag.cloud/posts/checkpoint-azure-routed/</guid>
      <description>There are many references for configuring route-based tunnels on Check Point and Microsoft web sites and forums but every one of them is lacking some sort of information or clear guidance on what exactly needs to be done. To better understand, current limitation of Check Point is that you need to use CloudGuard IaaS High Availability [4] in order to use IPSEC VPN’s.
First, one important fact to know is that the Azure Virtual Network will fragment the packets at 1,400 bytes, irrelevant of the guest operating NIC configuration [1].</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>